Guide to the Poly Archives Historic Photograph Collection RG.026
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series VII: Events
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous Events
    - Spotlight on Scholars, 1999 March 20; cuid933 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Summer Research Closing Ceremonies, 1998; cuid934 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Symbol Wireless Technology, 2000 July; cuid935 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Symbol Wireless Technologies Barbeque 2001, 2001 April 25; cuid936 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Taiwan Visit, 1996 January 23; cuid937 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Teacher's Computer Seminar, 2000 June 28; cuid938 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Time Capsule, 1960; cuid939 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Tri-tech Agreement, 1984; cuid940 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - United Technologies- Norden Systems, Grant Presentation, 1984; cuid941 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Unity Day 2001, 2001 September 19; cuid942 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Unity Day 2002, 2002 September 11; cuid943 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - USI Opening Session, 2002 October 7; cuid944 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Vision 2000, undated; cuid945 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Welcome Back Reception, 1995 September 14; cuid946 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Westchester Expo, 1997; cuid947 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Series VIII: Miscellaneous, negatives, and contact sheets
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated; cuid948 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, Non-Poly, undated; cuid949 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, undated; cuid950 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, undated; cuid951 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, undated; cuid952 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets, undated; cuid953 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid954 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid955 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid956 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid957 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated; cuid958 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Slides, undated; cuid959 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Photo Labels without Photos, undated; cuid960 (Box 22, Folder 37)